Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art buildings and grounds records, 1870-2007 COR0007.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Special projects, Series 10
  - New York Avenue Rendering, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Scheduling- NY Ave, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Schnabel Proposal, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Shefferman & Bigelson Co., circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - NY Ave Bldg Soft Cost Idea, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - NY Ave Bldg Storage- G, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Space Plan, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - NY Ave Bldg/Storage, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Studley Licensing Agreement, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - New York Ave. Tax Issues, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - NY Ave/Tenant Work letter, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - NY Ave/Telephone, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - United Unions Issues, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Hyman Test Pits, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - New York Ave. Bldg. Trash Infor., circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Valye Engineering Comparisons, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - New York Ave. Utilities Imform., circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Industrial Hygiene Survey Report Asbestos Abatement Monitoring and Air Sampling, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folders 20-21)
  - Industrial Hygiene Survey Report Abestos Investigation of the Corcoran Basement, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Willard - blue pencil landscape, 1985; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - NY Ave/Legal Fees, 1991; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - New York Ave. Zoning Inform., circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - United Unions v. Corcoran Civil Action, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - New Building United Unions Inc. Agreement- Corcoran Gallery, 1970-1975; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - United Unions Lawsuit, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - United Unions/Lawsuit & Settlement, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - ATEC/Asbestos, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Commerical Market Research Shannon & Luchs, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Misc. Publications & Memoradum, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Financial Projections NY Ave Bldg., circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Appraisal- NY Ave Bldg by Harps & Harps, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Architectural Plans Hartman-Cox, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - IFPRI Lease, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NY Ave Bldg. Financial Projections, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Lease Proposal/IFPRI, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art "Office" Building, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Joint Venture/Summit Resouces, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Lawyers for IFPRI Ginsburg, Felpmann, Bress, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Lease/"Standard Form" Wilkes Artis Hedrick, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Letter of Intent CGA/IFPRI, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Loan Denial CH-Chase/IFPRI, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Project Summary Books, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Proposal- Shearman & Sterling, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Security System, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Studley Brochure, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Feasability Study April 25, 1986, 1986 April 25; Series 10 (Box 26, Folders 1-2)
  - General Leasing Information, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Office Building, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - NY Ave Project- Permits, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Square, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - NY Ave/Octagon Concerns, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Memoradums & Correspondence- NY Ave Bldg., circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Monument Lighting, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - New York Avenue Parking, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Gallery Bldg. Permit, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Lands Art Numbers, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Broker's Party Report, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Certificate of Insurance Liberty Mutual- Foundation Test Service, Inc., circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - NY Ave Bldg Insurance, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - International Food Research Institute, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Jackson Parking Lot, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Building & Grounds Correspondence, 1987; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - HCB Value Engineering Report Feasibility Study, 1986; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Leasing Status, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Possible Rentals, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Corcoran vs. United Union, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Project Managers Responses, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - NY Ave Bldg Project Schedule, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - NY Avenue Bldg.- Riggs File, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Photogrammitry Dennett, Mufsiq, Ryan, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - New York Avenue Bldg Pepco File, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Corcoran Parking, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Marble Cleaning/East Coast, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - New York Ave Bldg. Security, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Seven-story Office Building, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Schirmer- Firesafety, 1988; Series 10 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - [SPEC BOOKS], 2001 November 16; Series 10 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - [SPEC BOOKS], 2002 October 25; Series 10 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - [SPEC BOOKS], 2003 February 7; Series 10 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - [SPEC BOOKS], 2003 May 2; Series 10 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Project Manual Prelimiary Technical Documents- Phase 1 Volume 1, 2002 May 31; Series 10 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Corcoran Volume 2 Permit, 2003 February 7; Series 10 (Box 44, Folders 2-3)
  - Corcoran Volume 1 Permit, 2003 February 7; Series 10 (Box 44, Folders 4-5)
  - Elizabeth James project files: AV, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Corcoran- Lay By @ E St., circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth James project files: FF&E, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Kitchen, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Electrical Lighting, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Photo Layouts, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Security, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Garrison Lull, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Testing/Probes, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Soils Report, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Major's Agent Hearing, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Subcontract Agreement, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Existing Conditions, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Johnson Controls, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Secret Service, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Schnabel Foundations, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Water Proofing, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Water Proofing Consultants, circa 2000-2005; Series 10 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Boroscopes, 2002 June-July; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Code Info, 2001-2003; Series 10 (Box 47, Folders 2-4)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Design Meetings, 2002-2003; Series 10 (Box 47, Folders 5-6)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Civil Engineering, 2001; Series 10 (Box 47, Folders 7-8)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Disaster Plan, 2001; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Hazardous Materials, 2001; Series 10 (Box 47, Folders 10-11)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Door Hardware Consultation, 2002 March 5; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Hazardous Materials Monitoring and Analysis, 2002; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Project Manual Asbestos and Lead-Based Paint Removal, 2001 November 2; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Washington Dulles International Airport Environmnetal Project Specifications, 2000 November 3; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Hazardous Materials Report for the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2001 August; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Elizabeth James project files: URS Insurance, 2001; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Aerosol Monitoring and Analysis, 2001; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Centex Construction, 2001; Series 10 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Elizabeth James project files: General Contractors, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth James project files: SF Analysis, 2001; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Structural Steel, 2001-2003; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Foundations-Corcoran Dewatering, 2001; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Metal Panels, 2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Corcoran Exterior Interior Finishes, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Structural, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Corcoran - Curtain Wall, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Smith Group, 2001; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Sprinkler, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Corcoran - Stone Interior, 2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Corcoran Exterior Stone, 2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Elizabeth James project files: CGA Concrete, 2001-2003; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Elevators, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Mechanical and Plumbing Budget, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Receptables, 2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Electrical, 2002; Series 10 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Elizabeth James project files: MEP, 2001-2003; Series 10 (Box 48, Folders 18-19)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Historic Structures Report, 1997 August; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Materials List/ Building Systems Schematic Design In Progress, 2001 May 25; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Materials List/ Building Systems Schematic Design In Progress Volume 2, 2001 May 25; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Material List / Building Systems Pricing Submission Volume 1: Draft Specifications, 2000 May 31; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Project Manual Preliminary In Progress Volume 1, 2002 December 18; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Project Manual Preliminary Technical Documents - Phase 1 Volume 1, 2002 May 31; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Project Manual Preliminary Technical Documents - Phase 1 Volume 2, 2002 May 31; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth James project files: The Renovation Preliminary Food Service Equipment Specifications, 2003 March 28; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Elizabeth James project files: The Cafe Preliminary Food Service Equipment Specifications, 2003 April 14; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth James project files: The Cafe Preliminary Food Service Equipment Specifications, 2003 April 18; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Elizabeth James project files: The Renovation Preliminary Food Service Equipment Specifications, 2003 April 18; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Elizabeth James project files: The Cafe Preliminary Food Service Equipment Specifications, 2003 April 4; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Elizabeth James project files: Material List/Building Systems Schematic Design Cover Page, 2001 November 16; Series 10 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Elizabeth James: Pre Con Buildings CTX, 2001-2003; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth James: Finish Samples, 2002; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth James: Budget 1, 2000 December 6; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth James: VE Budget reductions, 2001; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth James: Budget 2, 2001 July; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth James: FOG/A Trans, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Elizabeth James: Corcoran Trans, 2001; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth James: Delivery Invoices, 2001; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Elizabeth James: Printing, 2001; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth James: ftp Site Info, 2001 April; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Elizabeth James: Budget 3 CGA, 2002; Series 10 (Box 50, Folders 11-13)
  - Elizabeth James: Corcoran Trans, 2002; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth James: Project Budget, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Elizabeth James: CPF Underground Utilities, no date; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Elizabeth James: Centex Construction, 2001-2002; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Elizabeth James: Martin and Associates, 2002 February; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Elizabeth James: Gehry and Associates, 2001-2003; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Elizabeth James: Corentini Associates, 2002; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Elizabeth James: Budget 4, 2002; Series 10 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Elizabeth James: Corcoran Art Gallery Mechanical Budget for the Addition and Renovation, 2001 July 10; Series 10 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth James: Schematic Budget Corcoran Gallery of Art Renovation and Addition, 2002 January 11; Series 10 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth James: Design Development Budget Corcoran Gallery of Art Renovation and Addition, 2002 July 16; Series 10 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Elizabeth James: Alternatives, 2003; Series 10 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth James: Pricing, 2003; Series 10 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Certified Report Prepared by Annandale Balancing Company, 1999; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Fillmore Building Bank Loan, 1997; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Construction Info, 1998-1999; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Building Contract, 1998-1999; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Transwestern Horizon Group, 1998-2000; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Sigal Package, 1999 March 26; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Transwestern Horizon Group & Sigal, 1999; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Floor Plans, 1998 November 17; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Owner/Contract Agreement, 1998 December 8; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Transwestern Horizon Group & Keystone, 2000; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Fillmore Ledger, Budget, 1999-2000; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Construction Info, 1999; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Corcoran Building Info/Materials, 1998; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Keystone Contract, 1997; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Fillmore Phase II, 2000-2001; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Construction Info, 1999-2001; Series 10 (Box 66, Folders 16-17)
  - Signal Billing, 1999; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Construction Info, 1999; Series 10 (Box 66, Folders 19-21)
  - Applied Environmental, 1998; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Horizon Partners, 1998; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Tax Credits Empowerment Zone Filmore, 1998 January 16; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Fillmore Building, 1998; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Fillmore Closing, 1998 October 1; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Fillmore Easement, 1998 September 16; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Reimbursement Resolution, 1999 August 24; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Fillmore School, 1998-1999; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Quinn Fillmore Architects, 1998; Series 10 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - "Charlie Rose" Frank O. Gehry, 1999 June 28; Series 10 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Final Presentation to the Architectural Selection Committee- Santiago Calatrava- Architect & Engineer, 1999 June 10; Series 10 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Conceptual Design Proposal for the Corcoran- Frank O. Gehry, 1999 June 10; Series 10 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Presentation Video Frank O. Gehry & Assoc., 1999 June 10; Series 10 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Architectural drawings, 1870-1981; Series 6; 325 item(s)
  Contains blueprints, drawings, floor plans, and details of specifications of the building's exterior, interior, and grounds. Many of these pieces are the original Ernest Flagg and Charles Platt works.
  - School plan office, 1972; Series 6; 6 sheets; 19 x 25 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 1)
    Architect
    Lago
  - Entrance remodeling plan, 1968; Series 6; 4 sheets; 18 x 36 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 2)
    Faulkner, Fryer & Vanderpool
  - Parking terrace, 1970; Series 6; 3 sheets; 21 x 31 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 3)
    Morse
  - Washington Gallery of Modern Art floor plans, 1972; Series 6; 9 sheets; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 4)
  - Photo lab, 1972; Series 6; 12 sheets; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 5)
  - Modification of E Street, 1971; Series 6; 5 sheet(s); 29x22 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 6)
    Shannon
  - Director's room and secretary's room, 1972; Series 6; 9 sheets; 26 x 27 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 8)
  - Wells Fargo protective services floor plan, undated; Series 6; 4 sheets; 36 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 9)
  - Storage racks, 1970; Series 6; 13 sheets; 27 x 31 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 10)
  - GSA exterior lighting site plan, 1971; Series 6; 12 sheets; 38 x 25 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 11)
    GSA
  - Steel roof framing and trusses (all steel), 1896; Series 6; 15 sheets; 26 x 42 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 12)
    NJSI
  - Ironwork details: truss X, hip rafter framing plan; general ceiling sections, 3rd floor general arrangement of roof trusses in hemicycle, Undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 13)
  - Drawings of suspended ceiling, 1949; Series 6; 3 sheets; 24 x 36 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 14)
    Johnson
  - Hip and valley drawing of roof, 1893-1896; Series 6; 1 sheet; 28 x 44 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 15a)
  - Wall plan showing truss seats, 1893-96; Series 6; 1 sheet; 28 x 44 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 15b)
  - School alterations, 1960; Series 6; 4 sheet(s); 22 x 36 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 16)
    Faulkner, Kingsbury & Stenhouse
  - Sketch of truss, 1893-1896; Series 6; 1 sheet; 34 X 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 17)
  - Cross section through building, 1972; Series 6; 30 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 18)
  - Basement offices, 1968; Series 6; 10 sheets; 41 x 30 largest (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 19)
  - Parking lot revision, 1968; Series 6; 18 1/2 x 29 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 20)
  - Floor plans, 1968; Series 6; 5 sheets; 30 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.008, Item 21)
  - Sub-basement floor plan, 1972; Series 6; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 1)
  - Art storage, 1972; Series 6; 5 sheets; 27 x 31 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 2)
  - Second floor plan, 1972; Series 6; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 3)
  - School plan, 1971; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 4)
  - Basement floor plan, 1972; Series 6; 9 sheets; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 5)
    NCL
  - Non-bearing partition, undated; Series 6; 21 x 25 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 6)
  - P-100 and P-2750, 1972; Series 6; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 7)
  - P-2750 trolley assembly, 1972; Series 6; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 8)
  - Storage racks, 1972; Series 6; 7 sheets; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 9)
  - Dupont Center floor plans, 1972; Series 6; 18 x 24, 19 x 25 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 10)
  - Proposed kiln room addition, 1962; Series 6; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 11)
  - Modificiation of E Street, undated; Series 6; 21 x 27 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 12)
  - Corcoran sale area, 1969; Series 6; 5 sheets; 33 x 17 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 13)
  - Rough sketch: modification of N.C.F.A. channel, undated; Series 6; 21 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 14)
  - Unistrut trolley assembly, 1972; Series 6; 5 sheets; 18 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 15)
  - Proposed Design For North End of Lobby, 1970; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 16)
  - Wilfred exhibition, 1971; Series 6; 21 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 17)
  - Third Floor Plan, 1963; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 18)
  - Sub-basement floor plan, 1970; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 19)
  - Corcoran Gallery Lobby, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.009, Item 20)
  - Proposed design for North end of Lobby, 1970; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 1)
  - Electrical renovations, 1965; Series 6; 27 x 37 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 2)
    Sullivan
  - Existing Power Riser, 1964; Series 6; 28 x 39 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 3)
    F. Sullivan
  - Detail of closet for store, 1969; Series 6; 20 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 4)
  - Remodeling plans: 1st floor, basement bathroom and offices, basement remodeling, misc. building repairs, 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 5)
  - Existing basement floor plans, 1968; Series 6; 24 x 30 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 6)
  - First floor plan, 1968; Series 6; 30 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 7)
  - Second floor plan, 1968; Series 6; 30 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 8)
  - Proposal for Art Rental Gallery, 1970; Series 6; 19 x 24 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 9)
  - Proposed parking garage, 1970; Series 6; 20 x 29 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 10)
  - Basement plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 11)
  - United Union Building, N.Y. Ave. plans, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 12)
  - Sections showing details of 1st story atrium ceiling, 1893-1896; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 13)
  - Details of main stair hall: 1st and 2nd floor ceiling, 1926; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 14)
  - Hemicycle alterations, 1915; Series 6; 3 sheet(s) (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 15)
  - Fragments of 1st floor plan, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.006, Item 16)
  - Lighting Equipment details, 1926-1933; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.010, Item 1)
  - Basement floor plan, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.010, Item 2)
  - Revised drawing of plans: section of student staircase, 1893-1896; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.010, Item 3)
    Flagg
  - Exhibition room, undated; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.010, Item 4)
  - Granite setting plan, 1926; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.010, Item 5)
  - Additions, 1927; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.011, Item 1)
    Platt
  - Revised elevations of E street roofs, 1896; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.011, Item 2)
  - Basement window sills, 1926; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.011, Item 3)
  - Window details, 1926; Series 6 (Box RG7.0-2008.011, Item 4)